A Guide to the Graham T. T. Molitor Papers FA074
Rockefeller Archive Center
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Education (Box 31, Folder 761)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Fair Trade Legislation (Box 31, Folder 762)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Federal-State Relationships (Box 31, Folder 763)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Flood Control (Box 31, Folder 764)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Communism (Box 31, Folder 765)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Israel (Box 31, Folder 766)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Latin America (Box 31, Folder 767)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Panama (Box 31, Folder 768)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Soviet Union (Box 31, Folder 769)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - United Nations - Admission of Red China (Box 31, Folder 770)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - United Nations - General (Box 31, Folder 771)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Vietnam (Box 31, Folder 772)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - General (Box 31, Folder 773)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Governmental Reorganization (Box 31, Folder 774)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Health (Box 31, Folder 775)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Highways (Box 31, Folder 776)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Housing (Box 31, Folder 777)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Immigration (Box 31, Folder 778)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - International Finance (Box 31, Folder 779)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Judiciary (Box 31, Folder 780)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Labor (Box 31, Folder 781)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Legislative Reapportionment (Box 31, Folder 782)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Maritime Construction Differential (Box 31, Folder 783)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Mass Transportation (Box 31, Folder 784)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Medicare (Box 31, Folder 785)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Mental Illness (Box 31, Folder 786)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Me-Tooism (Box 31, Folder 787)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Military Pay (Box 31, Folder 788)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Minimum Wage (Box 31, Folder 789)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Mining (Box 31, Folder 790)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - National Defense (Box 31, Folder 791)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Obscene Materials Controls (Box 31, Folder 792)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Parks (Box 31, Folder 793)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Political Stripe (Box 31, Folder 794)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Post Office (Box 31, Folder 795)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Poverty (Box 31, Folder 796)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Prayer Bath (Box 31, Folder 797)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Public Lands (Box 31, Folder 798)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Public Power (Box 31, Folder 799)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Public Works (Box 31, Folder 800)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Regional (Interstate Compacts) (Box 31, Folder 801)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Right to Work (Box 31, Folder 802)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Right Wing (Box 31, Folder 803)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Rules Committee Packing (Box 31, Folder 804)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Science Program (Box 31, Folder 805)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Small Business (Box 31, Folder 806)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Smoking (Box 31, Folder 807)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Social Security (Box 31, Folder 808)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Space Program (Box 31, Folder 809)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Taxes (Box 31, Folder 810)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Test Ban Treaty (Box 31, Folder 811)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Transportation (Box 31, Folder 812)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Unemployment (Box 31, Folder 813)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Urban Affairs (Aid to Depressed Areas) (Box 31, Folder 814)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Veterans (Box 31, Folder 815)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Water Pollution (Box 31, Folder 816)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Welfare (Box 31, Folder 817)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Women's Rights (Box 31, Folder 818)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Youth (Box 31, Folder 819)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Position Summaries (Box 31, Folder 820)
- William Scranton - Positions on Issues - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 821)
- William Scranton - Bill File (Box 31, Folder 822)
- William Scranton - Campaign Literature (Box 31, Folder 823)
- William Scranton - Candidacy File (Box 31, Folder 824)
- William Scranton - Congressional Record File (Box 31, Folder 825)
- William Scranton - Convention Material (Box 31, Folder 826)
- William Scranton - Pre-Convention Schedule (Box 31, Folder 827)
- William Scranton - Transcripts, Interviews, and Speeches, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 828)
- William Scranton - Transcripts, Interviews, and Speeches, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 829)
- William Scranton - Transcripts, Interviews, and Speeches, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 830)
- Other Political Personalities - Bobby Baker (Box 32, Folder 831)
- Other Political Personalities - Mark Andrews (Box 32, Folder 832)
- Other Political Personalities - Cotton Interviews (Box 32, Folder 833)
- Other Political Personalities - Dwight Eisenhower (Box 32, Folder 834)
- Other Political Personalities - Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 32, Folder 835)
- Other Political Personalities - Lyndon B. Johnson, 1965-1968 (Box 32, Folder 835A)
- Other Political Personalities - Senator Kuchell - Memo (Box 32, Folder 835B)
- Other Political Personalities - Senator Kuchell - Analysis (Box 32, Folder 836)
- Other Political Personalities - John Lindsay, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 837)
- Other Political Personalities - Miscellaneous Files (Box 32, Folder 838)
- Other Political Personalities - Percy, Charles H., 1964-1968 (Box 32, Folder 839)
- Other Political Personalities - Earl Warren, Called "Socialist" (Box 32, Folder 840)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Cotton-Goldwater (Box 32, Folder 841)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Eisenhower-Goldwater (Box 32, Folder 842)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Eisenhower-Goldwater-Rockefeller (Box 32, Folder 843)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Eisenhower-Nixon (Box 32, Folder 844)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Kennedy (Box 32, Folder 845)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Lodge (Box 32, Folder 846)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Nixon (Box 32, Folder 847)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Rockefeller (Box 32, Folder 848)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Rockefeller-Taft (Box 32, Folder 849)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Scranton (Box 32, Folder 850)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Smith (Box 32, Folder 851)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Taft, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 852)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Taft, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 853)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Goldwater-Stassen (Box 32, Folder 854)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - H. Voting Record (LBJ-HHH) (Box 32, Folder 855)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Humphrey-McCarthy-Nixon (Box 32, Folder 856)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Kennedy-Nixon (Box 32, Folder 857)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - McCarthy-Rockefeller (Box 32, Folder 858)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Nixon-Rockefeller, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 859)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Nixon-Rockefeller, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 860)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Nixon-Rockefeller, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 861)
- Candidate Comparisons and Inter-Candidate Relations - Reagan-Rockefeller (Box 32, Folder 862)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1960: Kennedy, Nixon, and Rockefeller, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 863)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1960: Kennedy, Nixon, and Rockefeller, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 864)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1960: Kennedy, Nixon, and Rockefeller, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 865)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1964: Candidates Notebook, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 866)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1964: Candidates Notebook, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 867)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1964: Candidates Notebook, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 868)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1964: NAR's Draft Platform Planks (Box 33, Folder 869)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Humphrey, Kennedy, McCarthy, and Reagan, Folder 1 of 6 (Box 33, Folder 870)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Humphrey, Kennedy, McCarthy, and Reagan, Folder 2 of 6 (Box 33, Folder 871)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Humphrey, Kennedy, McCarthy, and Reagan, Folder 3 of 6 (Box 33, Folder 872)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Humphrey, Kennedy, McCarthy, and Reagan, Folder 4 of 6 (Box 33, Folder 873)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Humphrey, Kennedy, McCarthy, and Reagan, Folder 5 of 6 (Box 33, Folder 874)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Humphrey, Kennedy, McCarthy, and Reagan, Folder 6 of 6 (Box 33, Folder 875)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Congressional Quarterly Candidate Book, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 876)
- Candidates' Positions on Issues - 1968: Congressional Quarterly Candidate Book, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 877)
- General Issues - The AEA (Box 34, Folder 878)
- General Issues - Congress Administration (Box 34, Folder 879)
- General Issues - Conservatism - Birch Society (Box 34, Folder 880)
- General Issues - Conservatism - Liberalism (Box 34, Folder 881)
- General Issues - Conservatism - Transcript Clippings (Box 34, Folder 882)
- General Issues - Conservatism - General (Box 34, Folder 883)
- General Issues - Constitution (Box 34, Folder 884)
- General Issues - Crime (Box 34, Folder 885)
- General Issues - Defense (Box 34, Folder 886)
- General Issues - Dime Store New Deal (Box 34, Folder 887)
- General Issues - Education - High School Dropouts (Box 34, Folder 888)
- General Issues - Education - Medical School Construction and Scholarships (Box 34, Folder 889)
- General Issues - Education - Research Memos (Box 34, Folder 890)
- General Issues - Education - Vocational Education (Overlapping) (Box 34, Folder 891)
- General Issues - Elections (Box 34, Folder 892)
- General Issues - Electoral College (Box 34, Folder 893)
- General Issues - Employment (Box 34, Folder 894)
- General Issues - Executive Branch (Box 34, Folder 895)
- General Issues - Firearms Control Act (Box 34, Folder 896)
- General Issues - Foreign Aid - To Communist Countries (Box 34, Folder 897)
- General Issues - Foreign Aid - Multi-national Approach (Box 34, Folder 898)
- General Issues - Foreign Aid - Peace Corps (Box 34, Folder 899)
- General Issues - Foreign Aid - General (Box 34, Folder 900)
- General Issues - GOP Mainstream (Box 34, Folder 901)
- General Issues - Scranton Convention Material (Box 34, Folder 902)
- General Issues - State Conventions (Box 34, Folder 903)
- General Issues - Vote Returns (Box 34, Folder 904)
- General - Issue Analysis Notebook (Box 35, Folder 905)
- General - Republican Party Reports - Issue Development Series (Box 35, Folder 906)
- General - Republican Party Reports - Foreign Policy Workbooks, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 907)
- General - Republican Party Reports - Foreign Policy Workbooks, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 908)
- General - Republican Party Reports - Foreign Policy Workbooks, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 909)
- Miscellaneous File - Miscellaneous Clippings, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 910)
- Miscellaneous File - Miscellaneous Clippings, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 911)
- Miscellaneous File - Film Negatives (Box 35, Folder 912)
- Miscellaneous File - General Issues (Box 35, Folder 913)
- Miscellaneous File - "Return to Graham T. T. Molitor" File (Box 35, Folder 914)
- Memos and Correspondence - Inter-Office Memos and Correspondences (Box 35, Folder 915)
- Memos and Correspondence - FHS Memos (Box 35, Folder 916)
- Memos and Correspondence - Memos Regarding BMG (Box 35, Folder 917)
- Memos and Correspondence - Miscellaneous Memos (Box 35, Folder 918)
- Memos and Correspondence - General Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 919)
- Memos and Correspondence - Answer Desk System (Box 35, Folder 920)
- Memos and Correspondence - Bibliographical File (Box 35, Folder 921)
- Memos and Correspondence - BMG Organizational Set-Up (Box 35, Folder 922)
- Memos and Correspondence - Budget File (Box 35, Folder 923)
- Memos and Correspondence - Contacts for Project File (Box 35, Folder 924)
- Memos and Correspondence - Action Politics Coursebook (Box 35, Folder 925)
- Memos and Correspondence - File Codes (Box 35, Folder 926)
- Memos and Correspondence - Handwritten Notes (Box 35, Folder 927)
- Campaign, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 928)
- Cover File, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 929)
- Newspaper Clippings - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 930)
- Political Cartoons, 1960-1968 (Box 36, Folder 931)
- Polls, 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 932)
- Polls, 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 933)
- Polls, November, 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 934)
- Polls, January-May, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 935)
- Polls, June-August, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 936)
- Primaries, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 937)
- Public Affairs Review, February 27, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 938)
- Democrats - Vice Presidency, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 939)
- Republican Party - 1960 Campaign, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 940)
- Republican - General Clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 941)
- Republican Conservatives vs. Liberals, 1960-1962 (Box 36, Folder 942)
- Republican Leaders, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 943)
- Republican Leaders - General, December, 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 944)
- Republican Presidential Campaign - General, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 945)